https://mycpc.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Skip to content Skip to secondary menu Skip to primary sidebar Skip to footerMy CPC.orgGet an in-depth look at leading smoke air purifiers for your home.My CPC.org
Air Purifier Guides
All Reviews
About
Contact
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy for https://mycpc.org
The privacy of our visitors to https://mycpc.org is important to us.
At https://mycpc.org, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit https://mycpc.org, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.
Log Files
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.
Cookies and Web Beacons
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.
We also use third party advertisements on https://mycpc.org to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).
DoubleClick DART cookies
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx
You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.
Primary SidebarSearch the site ...
FacebookGoogle+InstagramPinterestTwitterYouTube
GermGuardian AC9200WCA Hi-Performance Air Purifier ReviewJune 27, 2018 By My CPC Vitaire H200 Hepa Air Purifier ReviewJune 23, 2018 By My CPC The Best Smoke Air Purifiers in 2018 – Reviews and ComparisonJune 23, 2018 By My CPC Alen BreatheSmart Customizable Air Purifier with HEPA-OdorCell Filter ReviewJune 23, 2018 By My CPC Airdog X5 Air Purifier Wi-Fi Enabled with Reusable Filter for Allergen ReviewJune 23, 2018 By My CPC AeraMax 290 Large Room Air Purifier ReviewJune 23, 2018 By My CPC
FooterFacebookInstagramTwitterYouTube
My CPC.org
About
Contact
Disclosure
GDPR – Request personal data
Privacy Policy
Search the site ...
https://mycpc.org is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to (https://mycpc.org) (amazon.com, or endless.com, MYHABIT.com, SmallParts.com, or AmazonWireless.com)
© 2018 My CPC.org
We are using cookies to give you the best experience on our website.You can find out more about which cookies we are using or switch them off in settings.
Accept
Privacy Overview
Strictly Necessary Cookies
Powered by GDPR plugin
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies so that we can provide you with the best user experience possible. Cookie information is stored in your browser and performs functions such as recognising you when you return to our website and helping our team to understand which sections of the website you find most interesting and useful.
You can adjust all of your cookie settings by navigating the tabs on the left hand side.
Strictly Necessary Cookies
Strictly Necessary Cookie should be enabled at all times so that we can save your preferences for cookie settings.
disable
If you disable this cookie, we will not be able to save your preferences. This means that every time you visit this website you will need to enable or disable cookies again.
Enable All
Save Settings
